everythingkitchens.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy | Everything Kitchens

## Privacy Policy

### Information We Collect, and What We Do with It

  * Information Collection and Use
  * Information Collected for Order Processing
  * Third-Party Sharing
  * Data Security
  * Use of Cookies
  * Collection and Use of Analytic Data
  * Protection of Children
  * Links to Third-Party Sites
  * Last Updated

**Information Collection and Use**  
Everything Kitchens is the sole owner of any information collected on this site. **We will not sell, share, or rent your information to any outside marketing agencies.** We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates as well as occasional low volume sales or promotions specific to our company. If you do not wish to receive any promotional e-mails you may [opt-out ](https://www.everythingkitchens.com/newsletter-unsubscribe/)at any time.

**Information Collected for Order Processing**  
Information will be collected from you to process your order. During this order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Data Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. **We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties** , except those specified in the Third-Party Sharing section of this policy.

**Third-Party Sharing**  
We may employ third-party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, postal delivery, review requests, e-mail delivery, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and **may not use your personal information for any other purposes than those specifically directed by Everything Kitchens LLC.**

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Data Security**  
Everything Kitchens LLC takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and offline. When you enter sensitive or personal information into our registration/order forms (such as your credit card number), this **information is encrypted and is protected with one of the top encryption softwares currently available  **in the industry: SSL. Everything Kitchens uses one of the most advanced forms of SSL software available: 256-bit encryption provided by Comodo.

All EverythingKitchens.com Web servers and database servers are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to these servers are strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by firewall's and password protection.

**Use of Cookies**  
We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our Web site, but you may not be able to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. You are always welcome to place your order by phone at (866) 452-4268. **We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party.**

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by EverythingKitchens.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party companies.

This website uses the Google Adwords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors on our site. These ads are served using cookies that include non-identifiable information about your visit to our site in order to show you ads for our products on third-party websites, including Google, and the Google Display Network. Any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy.

You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). You can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Collection and Use of Analytic Data**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and **we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.**

**Protection of Children**  
Everything Kitchens does not sell products for purchase by children. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use EverythingKitchens.com in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. **Everything Kitchens is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.**

**Links to Third-Party Sites**  
Everything Kitchens' Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that EverythingKtichens.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**Special Offers / Opt-Out**  
To honor the privacy of our customers, we offer the option not to receive these types of communications. All special offers are sent via e-mail and include an [opt-out link](https://www.everythingkitchens.com/newsletter-unsubscribe/) if you no longer wish to receive special offers and news from Everything Kitchens.

**Last Updated**  
The Privacy Policy contained herein became officially effective April 20, 2010, and was last updated January 22, 2013.
